Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Cross-Country (Men's/Women's) photos
    - 1992
      - Michigan Invitational 10/18/1992 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1993
      - Michigan Interregional 10/17/1993 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1993
      - Michigan Open 9/06/1995 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1995
      - Michigan Open 9/06/1995 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1996
      - Michigan Invitational 10/20/1996 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1997
      - Michigan Invitational 9/06/1997 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Wolverine Inter-regional 10/18/1997 (M), negatives (Box 52)
    - 1998
      - Wolverine Invitational 10/18/1997 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Big Ten Meet 11/01/1998 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1999
      - Wolverine Inter-regional 10/17/1999 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 2000
      - Wolverine Inter-regional 10/15/2000 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
  - Swimming and Diving
    - 1973
      - Indiana, ?/1973 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1974/75
      - Indiana 2/1975 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1975/76
      - Michigan State 1/1976 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1976/77
      - Wisconsin 2/1977 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1977/78
      - Central Michigan 12/1977 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Oakland 12/1977 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1978/79
      - Indiana 1/1979 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Schroeder 1/1979 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Wisconsin 1/1979 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Big 10 Championships 2/1979 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1979/80
      - Michigan State 1/1980 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1980/81
      - Indiana 1/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Wisconsin 1/1981 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Ohio State 2/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1981/82
      - Ohio State 1/1982 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Michigan State 2/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1983/84
      - Michigan State 1/1984 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Iowa 2/1984 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1984-1985
      - Pittsburgh 11/1984 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Indiana 1/1985 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Indiana 1/1985 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1985-1986
      - Iowa 11/1985 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Iowa 2/1986 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1986-1987
      - Illinois 1/1987 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Oakland 1/1987 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1987-1988
      - Stanford 1/16/1988 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1988-1989
      - Michigan Invitational 12/03/1988 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Big Tens 2/1989 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1989-1990
      - Eastern Michigan 12/08/1989 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Stanford 1/13/1990 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Big Tens 3/03/1990 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1990-1991
      - Michigan Invitational 12/09/1990 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Michigan State 1/19/1991 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1991-1992
      - Stanford 1/17/1992 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Stanford 1/17/1992 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - Eastern Michigan 1/31/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 53)
      - 1991-92 contacts (team and ind. shots), photos, contact sheets (Box 53)
    - 1992-1993
      - Speedo Cup 12/03/1992 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Notre Dame 2/05/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Ohio State 2/13/1993 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Big Tens 2/1993 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1993-1994
      - Gustavo Borges, Rodney Van Tassell, Brice Kopas, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - U.S. Open 12/03/1993 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Stanford 1/14/1994 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1994-1995
      - Northwestern 11/11/1994 (W), contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Wisconsin 11/12/1994 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Texas 11/19/1994 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - South Carolina 1/07/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1995/96
      - Stanford 10/21/1995 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Purdue 1/02/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - OSU 2/03/1996 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Big Ten Championships 2/1996 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - NCAA 3/1996 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1996/97
      - Texas 11/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Eastern Michigan 11/09/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Tennessee 11/09/1996 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Georgia 1/18/1997 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Notre Dame, Eastern Michigan 2/01/1997 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
        (shot by Paul Jaronski)
    - 1997/98
      - Penn State 11/21/1997 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Notre Dame 1/31/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Indiana 1/31/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - MSU 2/06/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1999/2000
      - OSU 11/19/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Big Ten Championship 2/24/1996-2/26/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
  - U-M Men's Tennis photos
    - 1975
      - 4/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Ohio State 5/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1976
      - Iowa 4/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Michigan State 4/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1977
      - Big Ten Championships 5/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1978
      - Illinois 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Purdue 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Kalamazoo 5/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1979
      - Indiana 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1980
      - Vanderbilt 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1981
      - Penn Tournament 2/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Wisconsin 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
      - Big Ten Championships (Horowitz and Leach) 5/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 54)
    - 1983
      - Minnesota 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Unknown 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1984
      - Western Michigan 3/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Michigan State 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1986
      - Illinois 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1988
      - Iowa 4/23/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1990
      - Northwestern 4/07/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1998
      - Virginia 2/19/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Purdue 4/26/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1999
      - DePaul (M) and Central Michigan (M&W) 1/24/1999, negatives (Box 55)
      - Northwestern 4/25/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Big Ten May 1, 1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 2000
      - MSU 4/05/2000, contact sheets only (Box 55)
  - U-M Women's Tennis photos
    - 1980
      - Big Ten Championships 4/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1981
      - University of Toledo 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1982
      - 4/1982 (Box 55)
    - 1983
      - Minnesota 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1984
      - Calvin 3/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Northwestern 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1986
      - Ohio State 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Grand Rapids J.C. 9/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1989
      - Purdue 4/22/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1998
      - Western Michigan 1/30/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Tennessee 2/12/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Wisconsin 4/25/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1998/99
      - Michigan Tech 10/17/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Wisconsin 2/28/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Indiana 4/10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 2000
      - Marquette 4/02/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
  - U-M Gymnastics (Men's/Women's) photos
    - 1973
      - Oklahoma 1973 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1974
      - Team Photo (M) February 1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1974-1975
      - Team Photo (M) February 1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Michigan State 2/1975 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Big Ten Championships 3/1975 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1975-1976
      - Team shot and Minnesota 1/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1976-1977
      - Michigan Invitational 1/1977 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1977-1978
      - Big Ten Invitational and Women's Exhibition-1/1978 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Minnesota 2/1978 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1978-1979
      - Michigan State 1/1979 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Big Ten Championships 3/1979 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1979-1980
      - Korea 10/1979 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Illinois 1/1980 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Minnesota 1/1980 (M), photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1980-1981
      - Iowa 12/1980 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Western Michigan 1/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
      - Wisconsin 2/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 55)
    - 1981-1982
      - Wolverine Invitational 12/1981 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Minnesota 1/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Big Ten Championships 2/1982 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Indiana 2/1982 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1982-1983
      - Russia 12/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Wolverine Invitational 12/1982 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Ohio State 1/30/1983 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Michigan State 2/12/1983 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1983-1984
      - Wolverine Invitational 12/1983 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Illinois & Kent State 1/1984 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1984-1985
      - Wolverine Invitational 12/08/1984-12/09/1984 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - MSU, Kent State, Indiana St. 2/10/1985 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1985-1986
      - Illinois 1/18/1986 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Iowa State 2/14/1986 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1986-1987
      - Ohio St. 1/1987 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Western Michigan & Illinois 3/1987 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Bowling Green 3/21/1987 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Big Ten Championships 4/1987 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1987-1988
      - Illinois 1/23/1988 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1988-1989
      - Quad meet 1/14/1989 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Western Michigan & Michigan State 3/12/1989 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1989-1990
      - Minnesota & Kent State 1/13/1990 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Illinois-Chicago 1/28/1990 (M&W)(M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Michigan State & Iowa 2/02/1990 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1990-1991
      - Illinois 1/27/1991 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Ohio State 2/08/1991 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1991-1992
      - Minnesota 1/11/1992 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Louisiana State, Northern Illinois 2/14/1992 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Louisiana State, Missouri 2/16/1992 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Michigan Invitational 3/14/1992 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
    - 1992-1993
      - Blue/Gold 1/15/1993 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Ohio State 1/22/1993 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 56)
      - Illinois 1/30/1993 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Valentine Invitational 2/12/1993 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1993-1994
      - Minnesota 1/07/1994 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - State of Michigan 2/06/1994 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1994-1995
      - Western Michigan 1/21/1995 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Illinois, Ohio State 2/04/1995 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Ohio State 2/12/1995 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Ryka Invitational 3/10/1995 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - North Carolina State, Penn State, U-Mass 3/18/1995 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - NCAA Regionals 4/08/1995 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1995/96
      - Blue and Gold 1/13/1996 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - unknown 1/27/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Georgia 3/09/1996 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Michigan Invitational 3/23/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1996/97
      - Illinois 1/26/1997 (Box 57)
      - Ohio State 2/06/1997 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Illinois-Chicago 2/23/1997 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - NCAA Regional 4/05/1997 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1997/98
      - Minnesota 2/14/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Georgia 2/28/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - MSU 3/06/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - MSU 3/12/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Big Ten Championship 3/20/1998-3/21/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1998/99
      - Minnesota 1/15/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Illinois-Chicago 1/23/1999 (M), negatives (Box 57)
      - Ohio State 1/30/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Michigan Classic 2/06/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Massachusetts 2/20/1999 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - Georgia 2/28/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
      - MSU 3/14/1999 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
    - 1999/2000
      - Maize and Blue 1/13/1999 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 57)
  - U-M Women's Golf photos
    - 1986
      - Big Tens 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1991
      - Wolverine Invitational 9/07/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1995/96
      - Wolverine Invitational 9/15/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1998/99
      - Wolverine Invitational 10/04/1998 (Box 58)
  - U-M Men's Golf photos
    - 1990/91
      - Michigan Invitational 5/11/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1994/95
      - Wolverine Invitational 9/23/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1996/97
      - Wolverine Invitational 10/05/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 1997/98
      - Wolverine Invitational 5/02/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
  - Lacrosse
    - 1983
      - 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - 2000
      - Tennessee 4/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
      - Arizona 4/08/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
      - MSU 4/08/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous Sports photos
    - Academic Achievement Awards 2000 (Box 58)
    - Softball Field and Stands circa 2000 (Box 58)
    - Bo Schembechler Reunion 1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - Basketball
      - Elks Shooting Tournament (Box 58)
      - Princeton vs. Southern Illinois 12/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
      - Pioneer, ?/1973, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - Boxing
      - 11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
      - Michigan Amateur State Championships, ?/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - Ping-pong
      - Chinese ping-pong team 1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
    - Wrestling
      - High school wrestling state championships (Box 58)
- Miscellaneous Athletic Prints
  - Football
    - 1970s (Box 58)
    - 1976 (Wake Forest) (Box 58)
    - 1977 (Ohio State) (Box 58)
    - 1978 (Minnesota, Ohio State) (Box 58)
    - Bo on Sidelines 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - Basketball
    - Hockey (Box 58)
    - 1993/94 Lake Superior State, negatives, contact sheets (Box 58)
      (includes good shots of goalie Steve Shields, negatives filed in box)
  - Gymnastics-men (Box 58)
  - Wrestling (Box 58)
  - Mud Bowl (Box 58)
- Slides and Transparencies
  - Football, Game Action
    - 1976 (Michigan State, Ohio State) (Box 59)
    - 1977 (Iowa, Ohio State, Wisconsin) (Box 59)
    - 1978 (Illinois, Ohio State) (Box 59)
    - 1985 (Notre Dame) (Box 59)
    - 1987(Notre Dame, Wisconsin) (Box 59)
    - 1990 (Illinois, Michigan State) (Box 59)
    - 1993 (Box 59)
    - 1969-1970 Bo Schembechler on sidelines and with Jim Mandich, Dana Coyne kicking in Indiana game (Box 59)
  - Basketball Slides, Game action
    - 1976/77 (Cheerleaders, Western Kentucky, Kent State, Wisconsin, Purdue, Indiana, mostly Johnny Orr and Bill Frieder on bench (Box 59)
    - Marquette) (Box 59)
    - 1977/78 (Central Michigan, Eastern Michigan, Louisville, Minnesota, Wisconsin, Purdue, Indiana) (Box 59)
    - 1978/79 (Western Michigan, Minnesota, Michigan State, Notre Dame, Purdue, Central Michigan, Ohio State) (Box 59)
    - 1980/81 (Michigan State) (Box 59)
    - 1981/82 (Michigan State, Ohio State, unidentified, and shots of Coach Bill Frieder) (Box 59)
    - 1984/85, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Hockey Slides, game action
    - 1976/77 (Michigan Tech, Michigan State, and unidentified, Dave DeBol) (Box 59)
    - 1977/78 (Denver, Michigan State, Minnesota, Wisconsin) (Box 59)
    - 1978/79 (Ohio State) (Box 59)
    - 1979/80 (Michigan State) (Box 59)
    - 1980/81 (Lake Superior State) (Box 59)
    - 1996 (Box 59)
    - 1978/79 (Northwestern) (Box 59)
    - Dave Porter(b/w, copy slide?) (Box 59)
  - Baseball Slides
    - 1979 (Eastern Michigan) (Box 59)
  - Tennis Slides
    - 1979 (Indiana) (Box 59)
  - Track
    - Mike Lattany high jumping (Box 59)
  - Swimming
    - 1979 (2 unidentified, Fernando Canales) (Box 59)
  - Women's Basketball
    - 1979 (Northern Michigan, Eastern Michigan) (Box 59)
    - 1981 (Bud Vandeweghe) (Box 59)
  - Softball
    - 1979(Michigan State) (Box 59)
    - 1990 (Patti Benedict) (Box 59)
  - Women's Swimming
    - (unidentified slide) (Box 59)
  - Volleyball
    - September 1995 (Box 59)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Marching Band, football crowds, tailgate parties 1978-1979 (Box 59)
- Non-Athletic Photos
  The Non Athletic Photos includes a selection of prints of university events and of musicians, artists and other visitors to campus. Negatives of many of these photos are in the News and Information Services photographs.
  The personal photographs in the Kalmbach collection include many family photos, nature pictures, and some experimental work using special films and dark room techniques.
  The family photos include birthday parties, holidays, the Kalmbach children and friends at play, confirmations, school pictures, family vacations and trips to the family cabin on Silver Lake. Examples of some of Kalmbach's nature photography include shots of Tahquemenon Falls, the Huron River, Silver Lake and forest and rural scenes from Northern Michigan. A number of the pictures were taken with Kodalith or infrared film. Bob's longtime interest n the American West is reflected in a series of photos of the Saline Rodeo. The personal photos include prints and negatives (many in 4x5 format) and are arranged alphabetically based on the titles on negative sleeves or prints.
  - Prints
    - Performers and artists (Box 60)
    - Campus Buildings and Events (Box 60)
    - Campus People and Events (Box 60)
    - Gerald Ford (Box 60)
    - Joseph Brodsky (Box 60)
    - Dance Studio (Box 60)
    - Old German Restaurant Fire (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 60)
    - Nature (Box 60)
    - Photos of Bob Kalmbach (Box 59)
  - Negatives and Contact Sheets
    - Family and Miscellaneous circa 1957-1974
      - Bardwick, Debbie (Box 60)
      - Bardwick, Peter and Jeffi (Box 60)
      - Bardwick, Peter and Jeffi, September (?) 1963 (Box 60)
      - Bear (Box 60)
      - Bielby, Stan, family (Box 60)
      - Bird buzzing at Schnierle farm 1970 (Box 60)
      - Blair, Jo Lynn (Box 60)
      - Boats, night shot at Milahokia, color (Box 60)
      - Boiler Replacement, Plant Department July 1, 1960 (Box 60)
      - Bottle in Window (Box 60)
      - Bridge (Box 60)
      - Cactus, Botanical Gardens 1971 (Box 60)
      - Cat close-up (Hank and Vernes (?) 1970 (Box 60)
      - Cat, T.C. April 1969 (Box 60)
      - Chryle's Confirmation (Box 60)
      - Chryle's Girl Scout Camping trip 1965 (Box 60)
        (Chryle's negatives)
      - Chryle with hurt robin June 1974 (Box 60)
      - Chryle and John, portraits December 1970 (Box 60)
      - Christmas Party at Photo Services 1961 and Fred Anderegg's Retirement (Box 60)
      - Christmas 1971 (Box 60)
      - Cloud Scene, Milahokia, color (Box 60)
      - Cloud Scenes, at home and U.P. (Box 60)
      - Clown, color interneg (Box 60)
      - Cow, two-legged (Box 60)
      - Cub Scout skit, Kim's den (Box 60)
      - Cub Scouts, Flora-Kim, at Navy Game October 1972 (Box 60)
      - Curtis, Peck, at Navy Game October 1972 (Box 60)
      - Cut River Bridge and Lake Michigan Scene from bridge (Box 60)
      - Deer season, Arrowhead 1967-1969 (Box 60)
      - Deer November 1971, 4x5 b/w neg. and color slides (Box 60)
        (Bob with gutted deer hanging in garage)
      - DenHoater / McNaughton families, picnic in backyard, July 4 (Box 60)
      - DenHoater, Tobogganing (Box 60)
      - Ditch and Constables (Box 60)
      - Dogs, Gi-Gi and Snoopy in backyard with Terri and Rusty (Box 60)
      - Dogs, Charlie, Snoopy, Kodalith and regular negs. (Box 60)
      - Dogs, Jennie behind fence (Box 60)
      - Dolph Lake March 1970 (Box 60)
      - Drum Major, 35mm and Kodalith (Box 60)
      - Easter 1971 (Box 60)
      - Eclipse March 7, 1970 (Box 60)
      - Elephant (Box 60)
      - Erbs 1954, 2x2.5 negs. (Box 60)
        (includes Shots of camping, fishing, water falls, an family)
      - Erbs,. 1966 (Box 60)
      - Events Building 1968, 5x7 neg. (Box 60)
      - Events Building 1968 (Box 60)
        (Crisler Arena)
      - Family, Bill Smith and family, swimming (Box 60)
      - Family, boys playing ball, Chryle's party (Box 61)
      - Family, Chryle, Rusty and Terri, 2x2.25 negs. (Box 61)
      - Family, Easter 1965 (Box 61)
      - Family, family shots 1956, 16 4x5 negs (Box 61)
      - Family, Grandma Rose 1972 (Box 61)
      - Family, Great-great-grandfather I Army, probably Civil War, copy negative (Box 61)
      - Family, kids and Flo's portraits (Box 61)
      - Family, kids and Storey kids, color (Box 61)
      - Family, Kids around Hutchins house July 1957 (Box 61)